♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Tonet] Ibyang is at my brother's shop.
She's still crying.
She just stopped your bratty daughter!
Hey, hey. Don't talk about
my child like that.
[Tonet] If you don't want the kid, say so!
Don't make her feel worthless!
[Atoy] Tomorrow,
I'll take you both out!
Where are we going?
Why did you even come back?
[Janine] You're not the real child.
[Tonet] Honestly,
her attitude is really different
from you and Atoy.
[Audrey] But even so,
Janine is my flesh and blood.
Uh, speaking of blood, there's…
There's a donation drive at the court now.
What's your blood type?
[in English] O positive.
- [teenager] Brother, brother!
- [Atoy] Oh?
[teenager] Can I take a picture of you?
You look so cute as father and child.
You even look alike.
I'm his real daughter, not her.
[Tonet] The mother and father
are both O positive.
But their child is AB positive.
Is that possible?
No. It's impossible.
So, Janine isn't Atoy's child?
[Martina] Isn't it unsettling that Atoy
has been with Janine for that long?
What if he notices or finds out
she isn't his child?
I need to talk to Atoy now. Wait.
Ah?
PREVIOUSLY
Atoy?
Ibyang!
[ominous music playing]
Atoy!
Ibyang!
Oh, miss! Miss?
Did you see a man?
He's tall, really handsome,
and he was with two little girls.
Ah, yes, earlier.
They were playing hopscotch there.
They already left.
Ah, where did they go?
I don't know.
[music fades]
[in English] Thank you.
[sauve theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[thumps and gunshots]
[clacking]
[snipping]
[electronic blipping]
[muffled chattering]
It's Gavin.
[Karla] Gavin.
How was your date with Cathy?
You're not telling me anything.
Looks like it won't work out.
Did she reject you?
[melancholic music playing]
You know what? That's okay.
You'll find a girl who's really for you.
Maybe you already know her.
You just don't notice.
Come on, let's eat.
My treat, so you'll cheer up.
Honestly,
I'm so happy because…
we're a couple now! [laughs]
What? You thought I got rejected?
This wouldn't have happened without you.
Seriously? You're really together?
Yes! [chuckles softly]
Isn't it too soon?
Just one date and you're already a couple?
Cathy decided not to delay it anymore.
I didn't expect it either.
[in English] But I'm happy,
and it works for us.
But you don't really know each other yet,
and she already said yes.
Sorry, Gav, but isn't that a red flag?
Come on, Karla.
Even if she's my girlfriend now,
of course we'll still get
to know each other,
and if she doesn't like
something about me,
we can work it out.
♪ Don't get ahead ♪
♪ Of what the heart feels… ♪
Gavsy!
[in English] Babe, you came!
Uh, can you take a video
of me while I donate blood?
[in English] So, I can post it
on my socials for awareness.
Sure, let's go.
[in English] Perfect.
Thank you so much! Let's go!
♪ In every game… ♪
"Gavsy"?
[in English] "Babe"?
Gross.
♪ Not that ♪
♪ I'm thinking badly ♪
♪ There are many like you… ♪
Hmm.
[slurps] That's it.
[clicks tongue] Hit the spot.
Exactly.
Here, Netchai.
[line rings]
Hello, Tonet.
Oh, just reminding you.
We're eating later at that
roast pig restaurant I found at the mall.
Twelve-thirty, okay? I reserved a table.
Okay, brother!
Yes, yes. I'm on my way to the mall.
I'm almost there.
Wait. What's the occasion?
[chuckles] Nothing.
I just exceeded my order quota this month.
So, I thought I'd treat you.
Let's celebrate. Let's eat Lechon Cebu.
Is that okay?
Isn't your cholesterol high?
We might end up at the morgue tomorrow.
[sneaky music playing]
[gasps, coughs]
What's wrong with you?
Eh-- What? You're exaggerating!
No, after eating lots of lechon,
we'll walk home to digest what we ate.
Then, if you want,
we'll chew all the grass we pass by.
Would that work? Huh, would that work?
But I just want to say, brother…
Congratulations to you.
It seems you really succeeded
here in Manila.
It's like your life
is on another level now.
Ah, wow.
Oh, fine, fine. Okay, okay, okay.
Don't forget, okay?
Twelve-thirty, okay?
Yes, yes!
Love you, brother.
Bye. Take care.
Yes, bye, brother. Bye-bye.
[phone blips]
Wait.
That's Audrey's.
[suspicious music playing]
Ah, sir!
Can we follow that car? Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[softly] Thank you.
[Paldo] That's it, that's it.
[man] Kuya Kurt's pares
is really delicious.
- [man] It's tasty.
- [Paldo] I'll take care of this, okay.
- Wow!
- I'll pay for all of this.
- [men muttering]
[lively chattering]
- [man 1] Yes, I got this.
- [man 2] Rice, please.
I told you so.
Oh, rice. That's yours.
- Do you want more?
- [man] So good.
Nothing else?
- Just order.
- More rice, more rice.
[man] Thanks, Boss Paldo.
- [man] Soft drinks.
- Brother Kurt…
[man] It's delicious.
I thought, um…
- your goddaughter, Denden,
- [Kurt] Hmm?
- [sneaky music playing]
- will be the one selling here.
[in English] How come
she's not yet here?
[in English] I've been,
you know, waiting for her.
- [chuckles softly]
- Yes.
I miss her like crazy, Brother Kurt!
You guys are unbelievable.
Actually, she's working on something
before coming here.
But listen up.
Behave yourselves
when she sells here, okay?
- [man] Oh, you guys behave, huh.
- Huh, huh?
Do you have other goddaughters,
Brother Kurt?
- [coughs]
- We can't all go for Denden.
Why are you even asking that?
She'll only pick one among us, you know.
- Who's the most handsome here?
- Me.
Then, it's Brother Atoy!
You disagree?
[playful music playing]
Who's the second most handsome here?
Ah, c'mon! Tonet just rejected you.
Actually, guys, speaking
of my goddaughter,
she's here now.
[sneaky music playing]
- [man 1] Wow!
- [man 2] Whoa!
[Paldo] Oh, my goodness!
- [T-Bak] Wow!
- [Paldo] Move, move, move.
[man] Ooh-la-la!
[Paldo] Hi, Denden. Hi, hi, hi.
- Hi, Godfather.
- [Kurt] How are you?
Is your head okay or still hurting?
- I'm fine now.
- [Kurt] Really?
Where's the guy who caught the thief
who stole my phone yesterday?
Uh, um…
[Paldo] Uh… [clears throat]
Actually…
that was me.
I was the one who helped you.
I just want to fix this barangay, so…
You know, I help people in need.
It wasn't you.
He's also the one who elbowed my face.
The handsome curly-haired guy.
[man clears throat]
It wasn't you.
[sneaky music playing]
Curly-haired?
Handsome curly-haired guy?
[music fades]
[in English] Sir Emerson.
[in English] Have you seen Tonet?
[in English] Is it okay if I ask her out
on a date later?
Hmm, mmm-mmm, mmm-mmm.
No can do.
[in English] You… don't, uh…
ask later for a date.
[in English] Yes. She's, uh… make crazy,
because, uh, we have a walk.
[in English] Uh, I won't do that.
[in English] I just want to ask her out.
[in English] No. No, no, no.
[in English] You-- You don't…
[in English] You… Uh--
Not possible. It's hard.
Simply no, because we have plans.
We have plans, so…
[in English] You better date her to ask
in the next time.
[in English] Uh, good luck. Better luck.
[in English] But…
- [in English] No.
- [in English] I just--
[in English] No, no, no, no.
I mean, leave, leave.
You go, hasta la vista. Okay?
[in English] Okay, don't shy yourself.
[in English] Okay,
good riddance. All right!
Speaking English is really hard.
[quirkymusic playing]
You're really hard to talk to--
Don't!
[music fades]
[security] Ah, ma'am, ma'am, ma'am…
What do you need?
[chuckles] Guard, I'm Tonet.
I know Audrey Regalia.
I just want to talk to her.
It's important.
All right, follow me.
[security guard] Let's go.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Sorry, sorry, sorry, I--
No, no, no, I don't-- [titters]
I don't cut up customers.
Uh, uh…
W-What do you need done?
[chuckles] Don't you remember me?
I'm the one you elbowed, then passed out.
I'm Brother Kurt's goddaughter.
Ah, y-yes! [titters]
Yes, right? Yes, right?
Well, sorry.
My apologies, I had--
I was talking to someone earlier,
and I've got a lot on my mind.
Uh, why… why are you here?
I just want to thank you.
Here, I brought you my goods.
[chuckles]
Do you want to taste this…
pineapple of mine? [chuckles]
Uh--
Mmm.
[playful music playing]
Delicious. Your pineapple is delicious.
[chuckles]
Hey, let's taste the pineapple too!
Yes!
- [man 1] Share!
- [man 2] Yes.
[man] Let's go in there!
[clamoring]
[indistinct chattering]
[Emerson] All of you, leave.
You're disturbing us!
[clamoring]
[indistinct chattering]
[Paldo] Wait--
Hold on.
[Emerson clears throat]
[chuckles] Sorry. Apologies.
You know, Emerson,
pineapple isn't the only thing
I'll let you taste.
[stammering]
[stuttering] O-okay, I'm okay
with your pineapple.
[giggles] What I mean is, other dishes.
Do you want to have lunch together?
[quirky music playing]
What? Uh…
It's just that…
No, I can't. I have…
I have a date.
[music fades]
My-- My sister, Tonet.
Yes, because we have plans.
I'm taking her out.
[chuckles]
You're such a sweet brother.
You know, that's rare.
Putting family first before flirting.
Are we flirting?
[giggling]
No, no…
What I mean is…
My sister is my priority now.
Yes, because…
We haven't seen each other
for a long time.
Now we're finally together.
I really want to make it up to her.
Yes. [sighs]
Ah, ah-- And… [titters]
Your pineapple is so sweet. Thank you.
Do you want more? [chuckles]
[quirky music playing]
Oh, oh-- It's okay.
Yes. I'll eat it later.
Yes, I'll eat it later.
Thank you.
Is Audrey here?
Ah, Ma'am Audrey is in her room.
I'll just knock.
What's your name again?
Uh, Tonet.
- Okay, wait.
- Okay, okay.
[suspicious music playing]
It's big.
[door lock clicks]
- [Martina] Hi!
- [Tonet shrieks]
[in English] I'm Martina.
Audrey's sister-in-law.
[in English] Sorry. Uh, how do you--
How do you know her?
Uh, Audrey?
I met her through Atoy, Janine's father.
- Mmm.
- [Tonet] I work with Atoy.
I didn't catch Audrey earlier.
But coincidentally, I saw
her car passing by.
So, I followed it.
[in English] Okay. Uh…
[in English] Must be a really
important matter for you to do that.
Yes, it's about their child.
Why? Is there a problem with Janine?
[in English] It's very personal.
[in English] Family issue.
- [dramatic sting]
- [sinister music playing]
[in English] Well, I'm-I'm family.
She is my niece.
[in English] So, she's also my concern.
Did Audrey have Janine DNA tested?
[in English] Are you saying that Janine
is not really their child?
Sorry, but maybe--
Who knows? Maybe the results
were wrong or…
the specimen was tampered with.
Let's just retest to be sure.
[tense music playing]
[in English] I think you should leave.
[music swells]
Oh, wait! Why are you telling me to leave?
I didn't even come here for you.
[in English] I'm not gonna let you talk
to Audrey and feed her with these
wild theories about her daughter.
She's already been through enough
emotional stress when she lost Janine.
[in English] And then, you're just going
to dismiss her child?
I was the one who searched for that child,
so I know Janine
is really Audrey's daughter.
[sighs]
All I want is for Audrey to be sure that…
Janine is truly her child.
Let's do another DNA test.
Then let's check the blood.
If it's correct, then we have no problem!
At least we'll be certain.
But what if Janine turns out
to be the wrong child?
She doesn't need to do that,
and she doesn't need to listen to you.
- [in English] Please, just leave.
- [dramatic sting]
Why don't you want me to talk to Audrey?
Are you hiding something?
[in English] Oh my God!
Just leave, please!
I'm not leaving. I don't care.
I'll talk to Audrey
whether you like it or not. Period.
Audrey, Audrey!
[tense music playing]
[knocks on door]
Come in.
Ma'am, you have a visitor downstairs.
She says her name is Tonet.
Tonet?
Uh, what does she want?
She didn't say, but she wants
to talk to you.
All right. Please tell her
I'll just get dressed.
Okay. Ma'am, here's what you asked for.
[music swells]
Where is Audrey anyway?
- This house is so big--
- [in English] Have you lost your mind?!
- Audrey!
- [in English] What are you doing?!
Leave me alone!
Don't you want Audrey to know
that you found the wrong child?!
Because you wouldn't react like this if…
you weren't hiding something.
Or maybe
you already know
Janine isn't really their child,
and you just don't want to be exposed?
Shut up! Leave now! Get out of my house.
- [in English] Get out of my house!
- Audrey!
[in English] Leave my house!
Why are you pushing my wife, huh?
What's your problem? Who are you?!
You're a trespasser, aren't you?
- Do you want me to kill you?!
- Whoa, whoa!
You don't need to threaten me.
Yes, I'll leave.
I'll leave.
[in Visayan] It looks like
you're up to no good.
[in Visayan] Doesn't matter.
[in Visayan] The truth
will eventually come out.
What did you say? Huh?
Ah, I said… you're handsome!
I have something to do, so I'll go now.
- Your haircut looks great…
- Leave!
You need to follow that woman.
She suspects something about Janine.
That's why she wants to talk to Audrey.
How did she find out?
I don't know!
[in English] But we can only stop her
from seeing Audrey now!
[in English] She works for Atoy.
Anytime, she could tell Audrey.
[in English] She's a ticking time bomb.
We can't be exposed.
[music fades]
[muffled chattering]
Oh, Ibyang, what about you?
Do you want to buy something?
I'm fine.
That's good.
Daddy, it's so cute!
I want that. Buy it for me! Please!
[Ibyang] Janine!
You've already asked Tatoy
to buy so many things!
He might go broke because of you!
[scoffs] So what?
Why are you meddling, huh?
Ah, I know.
You're jealous.
Daddy can afford it.
He has lots of money.
[sneaky music playing]
Ah, Janine, my dear.
Just because we have money
and can spend doesn't mean
we should buy everything.
We should only get what we need, okay?
Hmm? Okay?
[in English] Okay, Daddy.
You little pest.
I have an idea.
Why don't we just watch a movie instead?
Wonderkids is showing now. I saw it.
What do you think?
G! I want that!
- Actually, I like it more.
- Come on, let's buy tickets.
We don't have tickets yet!
Looks like it's starting in…
ten minutes. Come on, let's buy tickets.
[bright music playing]
[Atoy] Come on, come on, come on.
Nanny, where's Tonet?
She already left, ma'am.
She was talking to Ma'am Martina earlier.
- What?
- [suspicious music playing]
- Martina, did you talk to Tonet?
- [footsteps approaching]
[Martina, in English] Um, yes.
[in English] Small talk, no-nothing much.
Why did she leave?
We didn't even meet.
I don't know.
She didn't leave any message.
She just suddenly left.
[in English] Um, anyway, I got to go!
- [music fades]
- [door clicks open and shut]
[tense music playing]
- [man 1] Come back here!
- [man 2] Bro!
- [clamoring]
- [man 2] What?! Huh?!
- I'll pay, bro!
- Pay what, huh?!
I'll return your money!
You're so hard to order around!
You're nosy!
[grunting]
[screaming]
[gasping]
[man 1] I'll chase you!
Jesus.
My lineage almost got cut off!
[ominous music playing]
- [horn blaring]
- [gasps]
Damn you!
[dramatic sting]
Damn.
So hard-- [shrieks]
- [anxious music playing]
- [gasping]
Ma'am, please don't treat me like that.
Already escaped death twice.
But on the third…
it will be final.
Is that a riddle or…
are you rap battling me?
[old woman] Listen.
The misfortune you suffered
is counted as three.
If not you,
then maybe…
the one you love.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[clears throat] Uh…
[titters] Um…
Oh, no, ah…
Ma'am, no. Um, here, take all of this.
Ma'am, maybe you haven't had lunch yet.
You're just hungry.
Better eat first.
Because sometimes hungry people
turn into poetic fortune tellers.
There's good porridge over there.
At Dexter's place. Just tell them.
[anxious music playing]
‪[Tonet gasping]
[music fades]
Make your men follow that woman.
Don't let her get close to Atoy.
[suspicious music playing]
[Tonet] Let's go, sir.
[car engine starts]
We'll follow you. Update me.
What's our plan for her, boss?
We'll profit from her.
If she resists…
you know what to do.
[music swells]
Roger, we'll take action.
[motorcycle engine starts]
- [electronic blipping]
- [tense music playing]
- Oh, Atoy-- Ouch-
- [man] Hey!
[Emerson] Hey!
[Emerson] What the-- Hey.
Stop! He's a thief!
[Emerson] Wait, my wallet?
‪UP NEXT
- Hey.
- Stop!
Atoy!
Where are you going?
You followed me?
[Red] Yes.
So come with me…
unless you want me
to put a hole in your side.
[Atoy] You really made me chase you.
Give me back my friend's wallet.
Keep the money.
The voucher. I need the voucher.
It's important to him.
Give me the voucher.
This?
I won't give it
without something in return.
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
‪♪ ‪Fix it‪ ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias